const ninth = [
  {
    number: 1,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-1.794ex;height:4.551ex;width:15.512ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/fdd490e03d8427a878c1cdfb26f7d178.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '54',
  },

  {
    number: 2,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-1.794ex;height:4.551ex;width:15.512ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/7e54691429643744832be96cd7bc2768.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '24',
  },

  {
    number: 3,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-1.794ex;height:7.854ex;width:9.736ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/5cab5319d02870869711cf591e994e04.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '20',
  },

  {
    number: 4,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения: </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.693ex;height:3.45ex;width:13.283ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/ab30f2bc367c4b6cbcd27e33fc3198de.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '399',
  },

  {
    number: 5,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.968ex;height:3.45ex;width:16.427ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/bd73db293fc0670659fca023db7a3a2b.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '6',
  },

  {
    number: 6,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.28ex;height:3.175ex;width:9.647ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/60a4170f80d9b5b2fbc559245002fbc7.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '6',
  },

  {
    number: 7,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-2.207ex;height:6.065ex;width:10.016ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/d715cca81e6ebf5c0ae7b1a86559232b.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '200',
  },

  {
    number: 8,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.693ex;height:3.037ex;width:12.159ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/727d786910a2f2f15467f09eb83bf7b5.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '64',
  },

  {
    number: 9,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.968ex;height:2.762ex;width:22.031ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c741ecf19b24515e285ecfe6c88aeb4f.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '4,5',
  },

  {
    number: 10,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-2.344ex;height:5.928ex;width:10.481ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/2c29876bb95b20888c3cae6b533820e2.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    number: 11,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.83ex;height:2.624ex;width:14.593ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/3ba1df85ce377eb1b893bbae71844eb9.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '4',
  },

  {
    number: 12,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.555ex;height:1.799ex;width:5.298ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/32666840668712d40c99673c07a70086.svg"><span> если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-1.794ex;height:6.203ex;width:12.531ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/12f8afb954e38a240e2161f8a5914f87.svg"><span> и </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-1.794ex;height:4.689ex;width:12.374ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/a034af788a39205cc2deaaa0ef4f515b.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,3',
  },

  {
    number: 13,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.693ex;height:2.211ex;width:3.684ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b3f1f5d7ea449033987d2436a030181a.svg"><span> если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-3.17ex;height:6.478ex;width:11.368ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/8aa45a1a62e2c89467cff3508a897c85.svg"><span> и </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-1.794ex;height:4.689ex;width:12.374ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/d464e3e2f10c34c0802295bb6be6ad6f.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,5',
  },

  {
    number: 14,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-1.794ex;height:5.102ex;width:19.061ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/372a77b7cb1cdba5ef071fbd57c8581b.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-13',
  },

  {
    number: 15,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-.555ex;height:2.349ex;width:9.173ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c8836ab0c39ad8f5ee6b0cc829d5bf4f.svg"><span> если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" style="vertical-align:-1.794ex;height:5.102ex;width:10.179ex" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/9948c56f9ee8f7bfc696c8b3e7db21eb.svg"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '23',
  },

  {
    number: 16,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/799774699edebdae9eeb0296546a95f5.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 22.699ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '2,5',
  },

  {
    number: 17,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/46b66006a81b4d583ab02c9c75d1077b.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 21.193ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-7,5',
  },

  {
    number: 18,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b34c95332d4502229721e5e255f20ff5.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.693ex; height: 3.45ex; width: 13.283ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '143',
  },

  {
    number: 19,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/3668bdaec467bb0655cfa961484673de.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.693ex; height: 3.45ex; width: 14.446ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '35',
  },

  {
    number: 20,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/f1dda097e353b8745f4daa6f4ef8009e.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.344ex; height: 6.203ex; width: 10.016ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '0,75',
  },

  {
    number: 21,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/dfbb02057c676cf10ea54632d6905e73.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.207ex; height: 6.065ex; width: 10.016ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '63',
  },

  {
    number: 22,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b033327d6063c0da4d511526bb38f8df.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 20.03ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    number: 23,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/7bc0477d74f0b479dad532ba66a0c983.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 4.551ex; width: 21.035ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '7,5',
  },

  {
    number: 24,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/03bab727727f924120d341c9a5e55c48.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.482ex; height: 6.065ex; width: 9.318ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    number: 25,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/614495cfbf329c1e70be294a74d2e413.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.344ex; height: 5.928ex; width: 8.156ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '2',
  },

  {
    number: 26,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/da4dd7c7e8c61196110116e9db0b69b2.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.555ex; height: 2.349ex; width: 6.075ex;"><span> если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b631c772ed159232b16528225a10e5ef.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.555ex; height: 2.349ex; width: 10.893ex;"><span> и </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/4b0a8b311f22d97f76471358ded28f58.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.074ex; width: 11.38ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,96',
  },

  {
    number: 27,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/5a1e621809d29767d5c15214b9245f4a.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.968ex; height: 3.45ex; width: 11.026ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '4',
  },

  {
    number: 28,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/4ed3f3fe67dd3a869bd20a6acd15fac2.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 3.175ex; width: 9.647ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '16',
  },

  {
    number: 29,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/40cb1dc0347f3e3584028b69a63ae97a.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 19.691ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-9',
  },

  {
    number: 30,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/6607f8b2a40bc3373b56ffd94f5af683.svg" style="vertical-align: -3.583ex; height: 8.267ex; width: 14.007ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    answer: '1',
  },

  {
    number: 31,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/823a2773c3cb935b6566a0ecaf23a73d.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.207ex; height: 6.616ex; width: 28.83ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '20',
  },

  {
    number: 32,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/6df9ec721821c11f379bd4f9862a8f4a.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.652ex; width: 15.387ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '2',
  },

  {
    number: 33,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/defbd96360edbd2731a8478ae7009e09.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.207ex; height: 5.515ex; width: 8.595ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/2b93e0ff1fb67e8286e5d512866e8ced.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.693ex; height: 2.762ex; width: 8.213ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '9',
  },

  {
    number: 34,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/449927a452ffc66f6ba4f26fa8bba6f4.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.207ex; height: 5.515ex; width: 8.595ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/89752434459ff7dd68d76fab26f7e59a.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.693ex; height: 2.762ex; width: 8.213ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '8',
  },

  {
    number: 35,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/5af21579af01cc35222c3b004d3d45f5.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.932ex; height: 5.652ex; width: 7.474ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/cf6f42d25ede1c323a2deb944c065835.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.309ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '46',
  },

  {
    number: 36,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/5843a0c102742400e18bb7dff75ee1d4.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.069ex; height: 5.79ex; width: 7.474ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/965c5c8ce699f0abefd404b7986489b4.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 11.146ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '37',
  },

  {
    number: 37,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c87be366684f856bb9fcf5475234af01.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.106ex; height: 3.45ex; width: 10.574ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b7dc6e5fb1a2ac7355354b54f38c4469.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 11.146ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-34',
  },

  {
    number: 38,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b6c2b6ea3b054d09a483531dc1556061.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.106ex; height: 3.45ex; width: 10.961ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/6d5b5adca00a9d4c867ff53b40923472.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.309ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-77',
  },

  {
    number: 39,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/a0e3ec568be54d8acfc850f696f8ecc5.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 30.02ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-5',
  },

  {
    number: 40,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c51cac39d8ce793ef8d5fd444801a7fa.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.239ex; width: 27.696ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-4',
  },

  {
    number: 41,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/4dad40caf617869ce62b9ce5960cf5fd.svg" style="vertical-align: -3.17ex; height: 7.579ex; width: 12.124ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '11',
  },

  {
    number: 42,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/9065310f2f811f2675815967f59cabff.svg" style="vertical-align: -3.583ex; height: 8.267ex; width: 19.64ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/1892ff1e910b36eb5efb5d37807ecc0d.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.555ex; height: 2.349ex; width: 7.826ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '4,5',
  },

  {
    number: 43,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/349e0fc8236ca0171bc9dce6d739019d.svg" style="vertical-align: -3.583ex; height: 8.267ex; width: 18.818ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/8c15b0463d129416d21f8ee694158284.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.555ex; height: 2.349ex; width: 7.826ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '1,5',
  },

  {
    number: 44,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/1f809b281454090fe8aeeceb03f2cff0.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.243ex; height: 3.725ex; width: 18.993ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '8',
  },

  {
    number: 45,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/2590d72505dc69c79ac959376b183b3b.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.243ex; height: 3.725ex; width: 18.993ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '18',
  },

  {
    number: 46,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/36a14d6b837e744213eb2889506a2ac2.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.751ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '12',
  },

  {
    number: 47,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/7c2621d6a4768068f7637fec72ebde91.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.751ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '162',
  },

  {
    number: 48,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/80588fbcb2e5ff9ebf0d76df92f5a41c.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.61ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '52',
  },

  {
    number: 49,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c063d560155b7dce2f4eff5afe8739ab.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 11.447ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '45',
  },

  {
    number: 50,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b4f790c8e0205c8e29fb254e9bf4f186.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 15.076ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '136',
  },

  {
    number: 51,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/13e8e1d180739ce9a052e9eaa9955493.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 15.076ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '208',
  },

  {
    number: 52,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/3c1bc65cf96b8407b3ef7232292eec14.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 11.447ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '189',
  },

  {
    number: 53,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/832c4ed08f3592732266acdc04bea0a8.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.269ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '80',
  },

  {
    number: 54,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/114232d9e37265325425e143140d34f2.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 10.285ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '108',
  },

  {
    number: 55,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/a47fb166694adf624801047d463c3e76.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.751ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '144',
  },

  {
    number: 56,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/2aa4c7177c5df056ee8168454c09a11d.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 14.254ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '136',
  },

  {
    number: 57,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/23b61ce9070589fb3761d118cb40f415.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 13.913ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '75',
  },

  {
    number: 58,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/42832617e308cd2ae8ad7c156f04769e.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 11.447ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '112',
  },

  {
    number: 59,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/54e92b4f43ca0fb8efb2de1038f97dad.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 15.076ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '208',
  },

  {
    number: 60,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/03756fbecd475f3f4545eb1fb53c10d5.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 13.913ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '40',
  },

  {
    number: 61,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Решите уравнение </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c0db509446d64d34d1a5d579ffd7c5c8.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 10.29ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '4,75',
  },

  {
    number: 62,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c6cb5b87a2a2ead66f48e55667072feb.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 10.691ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '162',
  },

  {
    number: 63,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/778288b101a473e73d7d668503e3acde.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 4.276ex; width: 10.071ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,5',
  },

  {
    number: 64,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/771dbf1672bcea3d21cc3e541826042c.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 15.626ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    number: 65,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/f0008ea0da86dc38aeb2dac484d3ad41.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.074ex; width: 4.331ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/7efabae269fdb3e095971af03a74d594.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 11.19ex;"><span> и </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/e5e79e313d50bbf679330b228b984696.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 11.634ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,8',
  },

  {
    number: 66,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/af7080aeed42c0e3d03887fc5c9f6125.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.482ex; height: 6.616ex; width: 19.338ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '0,5',
  },

  {
    number: 67,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b280f59e1b95d3249666f13fa1d00e1f.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 5.531ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/501e88c847a196186bd23bb3d179a963.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 9.625ex;"><span>, </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/462ae434aed4ab635de8be0b2531a265.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 9.551ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '1,6',
  },

  {
    number: 68,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/905017598639cd4b9ee6395c73cf4c3b.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 4.001ex; width: 14.404ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-48,4',
  },

  {
    number: 69,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/d7c5686d956758447df140335f838f35.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 14.938ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '2',
  },

  {
    number: 70,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/89420776776bd87b7baa096c107dc14f.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.074ex; width: 28.29ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,25',
  },

  {
    number: 71,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/cc24a8f4cc42ed11644ac2cd04ed0875.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.83ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 29.139ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '4',
  },

  {
    number: 72,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/3f213537905f4280fa7b40bbd3ed0a66.svg" style="vertical-align: -3.17ex; height: 7.579ex; width: 25.896ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-9',
  },

  {
    number: 73,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/21877cb845c9f41e81b21a8042afad92.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.968ex; height: 3.45ex; width: 13.67ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '80',
  },

  {
    number: 74,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/723267fee1b1c7cd6f2205fa0e392b6f.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 11.518ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '4,9',
  },

  {
    number: 75,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Вычислите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/fa33f5e4b338996e791b9c5a301cd76e.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.968ex; height: 4.414ex; width: 9.589ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,25',
  },

  {
    number: 76,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/4ff5e045eca773baf44737aa8f173882.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.61ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '153',
  },

  {
    number: 77,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/4b3572afe4226e8a8e6db0996c03ca08.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 13.913ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '200',
  },

  {
    number: 78,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/9d44c590a71807f0d6e2cad8d68aeb47.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.751ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '144',
  },

  {
    number: 79,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c8aa3758367227d7213bc4e022b82fb9.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.61ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '275',
  },

  {
    number: 80,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/e69c2cf3a95ed75f8ce9a3d38080add3.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 11.107ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '48',
  },

  {
    number: 81,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/cd3a2b846bc2414f0cf67dacb43f95c9.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 13.913ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '56',
  },

  {
    number: 82,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/4492432a87e44b46914170632be70a85.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.269ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '20',
  },

  {
    number: 83,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/d3cf35d4ea0bd6a0267ecaf6db7f33d0.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 15.076ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '68',
  },

  {
    number: 84,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/2652aa54035ef4f2573110a0798d8a02.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 15.076ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '99',
  },

  {
    number: 85,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/0bc5f19d88c7319acf62bc98e9eef4a4.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.61ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '152',
  },

  {
    number: 86,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/67d8d544e1267e7a6fab7970de018646.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 15.076ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '136',
  },

  {
    number: 87,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/6e322cf2f31e8def101a12027230bb34.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 11.447ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '112',
  },

  {
    number: 88,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/d237d076d9a6b281ea9256ecc4656a3e.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 13.913ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '80',
  },

  {
    number: 89,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/e0d3e9e0f427d4523dede345d79ae739.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.61ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '176',
  },

  {
    number: 90,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/60e27d204db3afe80690146bf266105c.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 12.61ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '242',
  },

  {
    number: 91,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/8cc4f5da472938942a15a70c16166df0.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.344ex; height: 5.652ex; width: 19.199ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '13',
  },

  {
    number: 92,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/66e0ff17ceafecf11d80d34f9d909efa.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.074ex; width: 5.493ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b631c772ed159232b16528225a10e5ef.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.555ex; height: 2.349ex; width: 10.893ex;"><span> и </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/08fa1a49c3db8743045c3d35275904e1.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.074ex; width: 10.798ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,96',
  },

  {
    number: 93,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/ca6b65f1c39d8eeca02b1e1bb474a4a0.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.344ex; height: 6.753ex; width: 20.087ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    number: 94,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/0fd5120fff90a23a45c509bdec307164.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 18.48ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '69',
  },

  {
    number: 95,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/8339d8068866aa1b2dfd671f1442d9af.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 19.642ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '54',
  },

  {
    number: 96,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/7953bd7f835e86ab29cb576753483c59.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.482ex; height: 6.065ex; width: 33.385ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-8',
  },

  {
    number: 97,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/44ec973f10bc24a1e1e96bfb3d88c34d.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.482ex; height: 6.065ex; width: 32.223ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '6',
  },

  {
    number: 98,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/2765802d592a7a875e13cc2c6f643d48.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.482ex; height: 6.065ex; width: 28.869ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/85f141fcdc76b5b6f448e5c843087f27.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 11.164ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '8',
  },

  {
    number: 99,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/bb50e32ebf2903f818d8b00406b09eac.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.482ex; height: 6.065ex; width: 30.461ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/bebbcc0cf199ab3d9848e054770317c1.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 11.164ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    number: 100,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/d2a6ca4a7d77cd20a3d3d062d2145250.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 11.404ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '25',
  },

  {
    number: 101,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/ded4c4772de73d63cd8d6779a2e7adcf.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 10.242ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '8',
  },

  {
    number: 102,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/664b6ebb756f7fee7de465a10a23a6a8.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.239ex; width: 14.923ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '0,25',
  },

  {
    number: 103,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/0be1f0318c2688fb383f43b1d2164661.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 20.424ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '8',
  },

  {
    number: 104,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/994f30c76e373303b3442a3062dd3126.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 19.691ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-5',
  },

  {
    number: 105,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения: </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/663e2d6ba7ef2eeadf41e8190253ed42.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.693ex; height: 3.45ex; width: 13.864ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '54',
  },

  {
    number: 106,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения: </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/00b6b3dc440c428a312b087d701169c8.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 3.175ex; width: 14.202ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '16807',
  },

  {
    number: 107,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/f0008ea0da86dc38aeb2dac484d3ad41.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.074ex; width: 4.331ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/e3e4904e24fb1bf90d268cb188ec3751.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.207ex; height: 6.203ex; width: 11.908ex;"><span> и </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/798596e63173031b8bede4b5803d4103.svg" style="vertical-align: -2.069ex; height: 6.065ex; width: 12.298ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,8',
  },

  {
    number: 108,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Известно, что </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/01c887580ecb4e5326332c4fd572b2d1.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.932ex; height: 5.239ex; width: 13.835ex;"><span> Найдите </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/b1299499d9ed85353ae7c39555e65545.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 4.551ex; width: 2.585ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-4',
  },

  {
    number: 109,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/188afbc89906efa06fcb43f14a3ed67d.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 7.98ex;"></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '6',
  },

  {
    number: 110,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/e34c50fc0d8ce42802962b6f83ee15fe.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 10.285ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '162',
  },

  {
    number: 111,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/c60f2d4859ec92157c16e4576ba1278c.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.28ex; height: 2.624ex; width: 8.42ex;"><span>, если </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/95c4974384d9f0f62dc66717a740222b.svg" style="vertical-align: -0.968ex; height: 3.45ex; width: 11.935ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    number: 112,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/f621f67294f5dffa9640add0f84f0925.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 4.276ex; width: 10.071ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '-0,5',
  },

  {
    number: 113,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/713f6c447307f501d2e922015bf51d45.svg" style="vertical-align: -1.794ex; height: 5.102ex; width: 15.626ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    number: 114,
    text:
      '<div class="Text Text_size_m TaskBlock TaskBlock_type_text"><span><span>Найдите значение выражения </span><img class="Formula Formula_img" src="https://yastatic.net/s3/edu/tex/8c147f8454a78716ef52764cd91f562d.svg" style="vertical-align: -3.721ex; height: 8.956ex; width: 14.959ex;"><span>.</span></span></div>',
    image: '',
    question: '',
    answer: '5',
  },
]
